怎么样  我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
So what do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
(忆往昔)
你要拿自己的灵魂换吗
You're offering up your own soul?
你只需要复活萨姆
All you gotta do is bring Sam back.
- 他们给了你多久  - 一年
- How long did they give you? - One year.
我不想下地狱
I don't wanna go to hell.
我们会想办法救你的
We'll find a way to save you.
艾德·扎德摩和哈里·斯潘格勒
Ed Zeddmore and Harry Spengler.
地狱猎犬老巢网
Hellhoundslair.com.
你们在这里干什么
What are you guys doing here?
What the hell are you doing here?
我们就该来这里
We belong here.
我们是超自然调查员
We're professional paranormal investigators.
我们只是想拿到书约  卖电影版权
We're just trying to get a book-and-movie deal. Okay?
把那玩意给我拿开
Get that damn thing out of my face.
- 快走  - 走啊
- Go, go, go. - Get out of here.
- 我的...  - 指环王啊
- Sweet Lord... - Of the Rings.
跑啊
Run.
别想了  我不会再去了
Forget it. I'm not going back in there again.
哈里  这是我们成功的门票
Harry, this is our ticket to the big time.
名声
Fame,
金钱
money,
性福
sex.
跟女生性福
With girls.
(如今)
[邪恶力量 第3季第13集]
你好
Hello.
我是哈里·斯潘格勒
I am Harry Spengler.
我是艾德·扎德摩
And I am Ed Zeddmore.
如果你收到了这段影片
Now, if you've received this tape,
你肯定是个大电视台高管
you must be some sorta bigwig network executive.
今天你走运了  先生
Well, today is your lucky day, mister.
因为你即将看到的我们自行拍摄的试播集
Because the unsolicited pilot you are about to watch,
是"真人秀"的勇敢新未来
is the bold new future of "Reality TV."
我们知道你在编剧罢工期间遭到了重创
We know you've had it hard during the crippling writers' strike.
懒胖猫
Lazy fat cats.
有我们这样的人  还需要编剧做什么
Who needs writers when you got guys like us?
我们的团队直面可怕的恐怖  为您带来
Our team faced horrible horrors to bring you
这段将永远改变你世界的影像
the footage that will change your world forever.
准备好经历电视史上最恐怖的一小时吧
So strap in for the scariest hour in the history of television.
你这辈子最恐怖的
In the history of your life.
准备迎接
Strap in for...
- 抓鬼特工队  - 抓鬼特工队
- Ghostfacers. - Ghostfacers.
(抓鬼特工队)
(艾德)
(哈里)
(斯布鲁斯)
(玛姬)
(科贝特)
(萨姆)
(迪恩)
(抓鬼特工队)
这其实不容易
You know, it can get kind of hard
平衡我们的日间工作
balancing our daytime careers...
和我们的夜间使命
with our nighttime missions.
对  但艾德和我在我们工作的
Yeah. But Ed and I pretty much call the shots...
打印店基本上能说了算
at the Kinko's where we work.
所以我们一般6点就能下班
So we can usually pretty much get off by 6.
- 嗯  - 每晚都是
- Well. - Every night.
对  6点
Yeah. 6:00.
以前就只有你和我调查案件
It used to be just, you know, you and I taking on the cases.
- 就哈里和我  - 两只孤狼
- Just Harry and me. - Two lone wolves.
两只孤狼需要...
And two lone wolves need...
其他狼
other wolves.
(第一阶段  准备工作)
- 早  特工队  - 早  抓鬼特工队
- Morning, Facers. - Good morning, Ghostfacers.
现在是晚上7点  哥们
It's 7 p.m., dude.
对于抓鬼特工队就是早上
It's morning to a Ghostfacer.
科贝特  怎么样了  伙计
Corbett, what we got, buddy?
- 我还在贴...  - 嗯
- I'm just putting up some... - Yeah.
这个要挂这里  这个挂这里
This has gotta go up here, that's gotta go here,
要全部铺开
gotta see the whole field.
马克笔  板擦  好样的
Markers, eraser, good job.
我第一次见到艾德
I first saw Ed...
是他在斯科根的特价店贴传单时
putting up flyers down at the outlet mall in Scogan.
我就看了看  然后我就想
So I read one and I thought to myself:
"鬼都是哪来的"
"Where do ghosts come from?"
现在  我就在这里了
And now, here I am.
艾德  你妹妹在虐待员工
Ed, your sister's abusing staff.
是领养妹妹  谢谢了
That's adopted sister, thank you very much.
艾德从我们还小时就一直痴迷于超自然
Ed has been obsessed with the supernatural since we were kids...
然后他跟哈里在
you know, and then he meets Harry at...
电脑营相识  俩书呆子就一见钟情了
computer camp and love at first geek.
我是斯布鲁斯
Spruce here.
好啊  各位
What up, player?
我有15/16的犹太血统
I am fifteen-sixteenths Jew...
还有1/16的切罗基人血统
one-sixteenth Cherokee.
我祖父是犹太教割礼执行人
My grandfather is a mohel.
我曾祖父是个假山制作人
My great-grandfather was a talus maker.
我曾曾祖父
And my great-great-grandfather
是个堕落的赌徒
was a degenerate gambler and,
还对佩奥特掌上瘾
had a peyote addiction.
好了  各位  别闲聊了  开始准备任务吧
Okay, people, let's cut the chatter and get on a mission.
好
Okay.
默顿大宅
Morton House.
一个大任务
One of our big fish.
(抓鬼特工队总部  晚上7:15  调研简报)
好  我们都听过传说
All right, we all know the legend.
每隔四年  据说这里会成为
Every four years, supposedly this becomes
全美闹鬼最厉害的地方
the most haunted place in America.
被称为闰年鬼
The leap-year ghost some call it.
鬼魂在午夜归来
The ghost returns at midnight
就在2月29日的凌晨时分
just as February 29th begins.
从没有人在那里过夜
And no one has ever stayed the night.
- 是吧  - 嗯  根据我们查到的所有证词
- Right? - Yeah, well, every testimony that we dug up,
所有目击者都在午夜前逃跑了
every eyewitness has cut and run well before midnight.
那一切即将改变
That's all about to change,
- 是吧  - 没错  艾德
- isn't it, baby? - Absolutely true, Ed.
- 没错  - 味道不错
- Absolutely true. - Mm, that's good.
法式香草
French vanilla,
那天你说你喜欢这个...
the other day you said how much you liked it, so...
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You are welcome.
我喜欢科贝特  真的
I like Corbett, I do.
来得早  工作认真
Shows up early, does his job.
很勤奋...
A lot of good hustle out...
我觉得他喜欢艾德
I think he's got the hots for Ed
那可能会给全队带来麻烦
and that could spell trouble for the team.
艾德更粗犷些
Ed's kind of the more rugged, with that
有金灿灿的
really golden...
美丽的胡子
beautiful sort of beard.
哈里挺好的
And Harry's nice.
29日
Twenty-ninth...
也就是本周五  特工队员们
Is this Friday, Facers.
我们想执行任务  就得马上行动  不然呢
We want this mission, we gotta move on it now, or guess what.
他就会再消失四年
He's gone for another four years.
- 怎么回事  - 等等
- What's this? - Wait a minute.
小心
Watch out.
- 爸爸  拜托  - 把摄影机关掉
- Dad, come on! - Let's just cut the cameras.
我们不需要这段
We don't need that. We don't need this part.
(第二阶段  潜入)
弯下腰  跟紧队形
Stay low. Follow formation.
好  不出所料
Okay, as expected.
很多人闯入过默顿大宅
A lot of people have tried to break into the Morton House.
所以本地当局受够了
The local authorities have just gotten fed up.
警方似乎把这里围得很严密
Looks like the cops have got this place pretty well fenced off.
(禁止擅闯  违者必究)
等等
Wait.
你们没申请到许可证什么的吗
Didn't you guys get, like, a permit or something?
许可证
A permit?
下次可以试试
That's a good idea for next time.
嗯
Yeah.
车
Car, car.
关掉手电
Flashlights off.
科贝特
Corbett!
好好
Okay, okay.
一动别动
Be totally still.
没事的
It's okay.
不是警察  只是乡巴佬
Not cops, just hicks.
- 不是警察  - 艾德
- Not cops, not cops. - Ed.
我弄好了  来
I got it, I got it, I got it. Come on.
艾德打开了
Ed's got it, Ed's got it.
伙计们  快走
Guys, let's go, let's go, let's go.
- 走  - 我们走
- Go. Go. - Let's move.
- 走  - 斯布鲁斯
- Go. - Spruce.
别动  安静
Still, be quiet.
- 那是厨房水槽  - 收到
- There's the kitchen sink. - Copy that.
好了  各位
All right, everybody.
抓鬼特工队  大家过来
Ghostfacers, let's line up.
都过来
Everybody.
我们就在这里扎营  这里是1号指挥中心
We're gonna set up camp right here. This is Command Center 1.
我们称这里为鹰巢
We gonna call this the Eagle's Nest.
走廊  1号摄像头就绪
Hallway, Cam 1 up and running.
看上去不错  科贝特
Looking good, Corbett.
收到  艾德
Copy that, Ed.
不客气
You're welcome.
好  斯布鲁斯  你那边怎么样了  伙计
All right. Spruce, how are we doing there, buddy?
地下室  检查2号摄像头  我的元首
Checking basement, Camera 2, mein Fuhrer.
玛姬  你那里没有影像  玛姬
Maggie, I got no visual on you, Maggie.
- 我是玛姬  收到吗  - 现在有了  你好
- This is Maggie. Do you copy? - There you are. Hello.
- 哈里  你活着吗  - 楼上  1号摄像头
- Harry, are you alive? - Upstairs den, Camera 1.
很好  合作氛围很浓
Okay. Good. I can smell syndication.
好  各位  我们在鹰巢汇合吧
All right, fellas, let's regroup at the Eagle's Nest.
(默顿大宅  晚上10:40  大本营)
好  斯潘格勒  开始
All right. Spengler. Begin.
好  检查电池
All right. Battery check.
- 检查电池  - 没问题
- Battery Check. - Check. Check.
- 没问题  - 好
- Check. - Okay.
没问题
Check.
看科贝特
Look at Corbett.
科贝特  哥们
Yo, Corbett, dude.
真帅气  科贝特
Looking good, Corbett.
- 你就像机械战警  - 机械战警
- You're Robocop. - Robocop?
- 你觉得我像机械战警吗  - 嗯
- You think I look like Robocop? - Yeah.
大家过来
Everybody, bring it in, bring it in.
我们都经历过这个
We've all been here before.
- 嗯  - 标准流程
- Yeah. - Standard walk-through.
- 1队  去西边  - 好
- Team one, west. - Okay.
2队  去东边
Team two, east.
- 是  - 好
- Got it. - Check.
准备就绪  开始行动
Spin the tires, light the fires.
- 嗯  - 数到三  抓鬼特工队
- Yeah. - Ghostfacers on three.
开始吧
Let's do it.
一  二  三  抓鬼特工队
One, two, three, Ghostfacers!
(第三阶段  抓鬼时间到)
(默顿大宅  晚上10:51  一楼: 1队  艾德和科贝特)
有人吗
Hello?
我在呼唤默顿大宅不安宁的鬼魂
I'm speaking to the restless spirits of the Morton House.
我们进去吧
Let's go in.
好
Okay.
有人吗
Hello?
我叫艾德
My name's Ed.
小心
Careful.
小心身后
Watch your back.
好
Okay. Okay.
看那边
Look over there.
你叫什么
What's your name?
0.3  0.29
0.3, 0.29.
我们身边现在有任何实体吗
Is there an entity or entities here with us now?
- 可以用某种迹象证明你的存在吗  - 呼吸
- Can you give us a sign of your presence. - Breathe, buddy.
- 我无法呼吸  - 科贝特
- I can't breathe. - Corbett, you...
科贝特  夜视
Corbett, night vision.
好  打开了  好
Okay. Okay, okay, I got it. Okay.
- 好  - 冷静  呼吸
- Okay. - Calm down. Breathe.
- 好吗  - 什么
- All right. - What? What?
让你脑海里的风暴平静下来
Calm the whirlwinds of your mind.
(二楼: 2队  哈里  斯布鲁斯  玛姬)
我们在进行基本的扫描
We're doing a basic EMF,
电磁场  超自然电子异象  温度变化
EVP, temp-flux sweep.
看来一切正常
Looks like we got all of our ducks in a row here.
怎么了
What?
摄影机出了点故障
No, this camera's fritzing or something.
奇怪
That's weird.
好了
It's gone.
- 好  - 拍下来
- Okay. - Get this, get this.
- 转门把手  - 好吧  好主意
- Turn the knob. - All right, that's a good idea.
天啊  天啊
My God! My God! My God!
就是只老鼠
It's just a rat, dude.
我不喜欢老鼠
I don't really like rats.
它们好恶心
They're gross.
老鼠就像这世界的老鼠
Rats are like the rats of the world.
那是...幽灵吗
Was that a...? Was that an apparition?
是鬼吗  是0.4吗
Was that a spectral? Was that a 0.4?
什么情况
What do we got?
因为电磁场简直...
Because the EMP was just off the...
天啊
God!
这一点也不好玩  斯布鲁斯
That is so not funny, Spruce!
天啊
God.
好吧  好像只是这根树枝
Okay, it was just... I think it was just this branch.
好
Okay.
就窗上那个
In the window.
- 真吓人  伙计  - 是很吓人
- This is spooky, man. - It's pretty spooky.
别动  警察
Freeze! Police officers!
- 别动  - 天啊
- Don't move. - God.
好了  别激动
All right. All right. Take it easy. Take it easy.
出示下证件
Let's see identification.
来  出示身份证件
Come on. Let's see some ID.
我们...
Why are we...?
- 我们被捕了吗  - 我们没带武器
- Are we under arrest? - We are unarmed.
天啊
God.
要解释下这身奇怪的衣服吗  科贝特先生
You want to explain that weirdo outfit, Mr., uh, Corbett?
我认识你
I know you.
当然了  拿出身份证件来
Yeah, sure you do. Give me some identification.
等等  我认识你俩  嗯
Hold on a second. I know the both of you guys. Yeah.
- 什么  - 嗯
- What? - Yeah.
我去
Holy ****.
怎么了
What?
西德州  我们消灭的那个幻像怪
West Texas, the tulpa we had to take out.
那俩差点害死我们的傻蛋
Those two goofballs that almost got us killed.
地狱猎犬什么的
Hellhounds or something?
- 我去  - 嗯
- **** me. - Yeah.
我们不叫地狱猎犬了
We're not Hellhounds anymore.
- 测试效果不好  - 艾德  这怎么回事
- Okay. Didn't test that well. - Ed, what's going on?
他们不是警察  伙计
They're not cops, buddy. No.
艾德  你不是有个搭档吗
Ed, Ed, thought you had a partner, too, didn't you?
不是这人
A different guy?
- 对  - 他也在吗
- Yeah. Yeah. - Is he around here somewhere?
- 他在这里捉鬼呢  - 好
- He's running around, chasing ghosts. - Okay.
听好  你和兰博得带上你的女友们
Well, listen. You and Rambo need to get your girlfriends
马上离开这里
and get out of here.
好吧
All right.
听好了  大胸男
Listen here, chisel chest, okay?
我们先来的
We were here first.
我们已经建立了大本营
We've already set up base camp.
我们抢先了你们
We beat you.
他们先来的
They were here first.
天啊
God!
- 艾德  - 嗯
- Ed? - Yeah?
你的搭档呢
Where's your partner?
(二楼: 卧室  2队  哈里  斯布鲁斯  玛姬)
10.6
Ten-six,
10.7了  各位  电磁场在飙升
ten-seven. Guys, the EMF is really spiking here.
温度降低了11度呢
Temperature's down, like, 11 degrees.
好  眼睛睁大了
All right. All right. Keep your eyes peeled.
可能要来了
This could be it.
玛姬  可以测下这里的读数吗
Maggie, can I get a reading in here, please?
有什么一直在扰乱芯片
Something keeps messing with the chip.
我不知道是怎么回事
I don't know what's going on here.
- 各位  - 怎么回事
- Guys. Guys. Guys. - What? What is this?
伙计  抱歉  没了
Look, buddy, I'm sorry. That's it.
相信我  那是全部的钱...
I'm telling you, that's all the money I...
(抓鬼特工队)
你们为什么来默顿大宅  艾德
What're you doing at the Morton House, Ed?
还是在闰年  你想什么呢
On leap year? What are you thinking?
我们是来过夜的  是为了我们的电视节目
We're here to spend the night, okay? It's for our TV show.
什么  好啊  太好了
What? Great. Perfect.
嗯  从没有人在这里过过夜
Yeah. Nobody's ever spent the night before.
其实  有的
Actually, yeah, they have.
我们可没听说过
We've never heard of them.
是的  知道为什么吗
Yeah, you know why?
因为在这里过夜的人
Cause the ones that have,
都没能活下来讲述经历
haven't lived to talk about it.
得了  我才不信
Come on, I don't believe you.
看  失踪人口报告能追溯到将近50年前
Look, missing-persons reports going back almost a half century.
约翰·格雷姆因赌约留宿  不见了
John Graham stayed on a dare: Gone.
朱莉·威尔克森  不见了  还有好多
Julie Wilkerson: Gone. There are tons more.
全都是来过夜
All of them came to just stay the night through,
都是在闰年
always on a leap year.
他们唯一发现的尸体
The only body they ever found
就是最后一任屋主  弗里曼·戴格特
was the last owner, Freeman Daggett.
- 这看上去像真的  - 就是真的
- These look legit. - They are legit.
我们时间不多了  伙计
Look, and we ain't got much time here, buddy.
午夜开始  你的朋友会死的
Starting at midnight, your friends are going to die.
天啊  天啊
My God! My God! My God!
My God! My God! Guys! Guys! My God!
天啊  我们拍到了
My God, we got one!
- 科贝特  我们看到了  - 什么
- Corbett! We saw it. - Saw what?
- 我们看到幽灵了  - 不是吧
- We saw it. It was a full apparition! - Get out of here.
4级幽灵显现
It was a Class 4, a spectral illumination.
简直太棒了
It was absolutely amazing.
他们不是德州那些混蛋吗
Aren't those the ******** from Texas?
对
Yes.
好的  我们去街对面继续说吧
All right. Let's have this reunion across the street, guys.
- 走吧  - 你们怎么来了
- Come on. Come on. - What are you doing here?
去买冰淇淋吃
Go get you ice cream.
怎么样  走吧
What do you say? Let's go.
伙计们  来  听着
Guys, guys, come on, listen.
你们该看看
I think you should listen...
不  看这个  正经的证据  好吗
No, no, no. Look at this. The honest-to-God proof, all right?
- 开玩笑吗  - 没开玩笑
- Are you kidding me? - Yeah. No, not kidding you.
- 我们拍到鬼了  - 读数怎么样
- We got ghosts. - What kinda reading did we get?
- 是10.9  - 10.9吗
- It was a 10.9. - 10.9?
对  10.9  快11了都
Yeah, it was 10.9, it was almost 11.
我出来一看  我想"怎么回事啊"
I came out, and I was like, "What's going on?"
- 我都...  - 看这部分
- And I was like... - Hold on, watch this part.
他被轰死了
He got blasted.
- 简直疯了  - 天啊
- It was crazy. - Oh, my God.
(萨姆: 我们是猜错了吗  那只是个死亡回声)
(迪恩: 是  但它怎么会在这里  有人在这里被枪杀吗)
(萨姆: 我是没查到有)
死亡回声是什么
What's a death echo?
如果我们有问题  肯定不是那个鬼
Look, if we got a problem here, that ghost ain't it.
嗯  那是真的
Yeah. That's real.
- 真发生了  - 死亡回声是什么
- Like, that happened. - What's a death echo?
回声是被困在循环里的鬼
Echoes are trapped in a loop, okay?
他们不断重复自己死亡的方式
They keep replaying how they died over and over and over again...
一般是在他们被杀的地方
usually in the place where they were ganked.
危险程度相当于恐怖片
It's about as dangerous as a scary movie.
所以回声或许并不危险  但还有别的危险
So maybe the echo's not dangerous, but maybe something else is.
是啊  好了  我们得离开了
You're right. All right. We need to get out of here, guys.
走吧  走  快收拾
Come on. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go, pack it up.
伙计们  时间不多了
Guys, time is running out.
我们走
We're moving.
那我们的设备呢  我们怎么办...
But what about our equipment? What are we gonna...?
我们拍到东西了
We got the material.
- 走吧  - 我们有各种东西
- Here we go. - We got all kinds of stuff.
- 我们可以请你们做常驻客串  - 等等
- We'll make you guys recurring guest stars. - Wait! Wait! Wait!
科贝特呢
Where's Corbett?
我想与这里不安宁的鬼魂交流
I wish to communicate with the restless spirits here.
灯灭了
Lights out.
我好像有夜视
I think I got night-vision here.
这样好多了
That's better.
不能丢下任何人
No man left behind.
那是科贝特
That was Corbett.
回复  科贝特
Come in, Corbett.
- 科贝特  - 不不  伙计们
- Corbett. - No, no, no, guys, guys.
科贝特  没事的
Corbett, don't worry!
伙计们
Guys.
该死
**** you!
你在哪  哥们
Where are you, dude?
- 告诉我们你在哪  - 科贝特
- Tell us where you are! - Corbett!
放开我
Let me go!
伙计们
Guys!
科贝特  快回来  科贝特
Corbett, you need to come back, Corbett.
快走
Come on.
(默顿大宅  午夜11:59)
(默顿大宅  午夜12:00)
科贝特...
Corbett's...
他不在这里  走吧
He's not here. Let's go.
- 走吧  - 我们走
- Let's go. Let's go back. - Let's go.
走  快点
Let's go. Come on. Come on.
- 不不  - 那是科贝特  你们没听到吗
- No, no, no. - That was Corbett. Didn't you hear that?
萨姆  快带他们离开  走
Sam, get them out of here. Let's go, come on.
- 很好  继续走  - 很好
- There we go. Keep it moving. - Looking good.
- 科贝特  - 好
- Corbett? - All right.
- 走  - 走吧
- Come on. - Let's go.
- 看好他  - 左转
- Watch him. Watch him. - Take a left.
走  快走
Go, move, move. Let's go.
关掉吧
Turn it off.
天啊  发生了什么
My God, what's happened?
天啊  他不见了
God. He's gone.
(默顿大宅  午夜12:04  2月29日)
他消失了
He just disappeared.
好  我们再看一遍各个角度
Okay. Let's just go through all the angles,
所有摄像头
go through all the cameras.
现在是12:04了  迪恩  你爽了  开心了
Well, it's 12:04, Dean. You good? You happy?
我是开心了
Yeah, I am happy.
"我们去默顿大宅猎魔吧"  你说
"Let's go hunt the Morton House." You said.
"那是我们的大峡谷"
"It's our Grand Canyon."
萨姆  我不想听
Sam, I don't wanna hear it.
你还剩两个月了  迪恩
You got two months left, Dean.
结果呢  我们要死在今晚了
Instead, we're gonna die tonight.
怎么回事  两位
What is going on, guys?
我来告诉你
I'll tell you what's going on.
所有门  窗
Every door, every window,
我猜所有能离开这栋房子的出口  都封死了
I'm guessing, every exit out of this house, they're all sealed.
为什么封死了
Why are they sealed?
这叫超自然封锁
It's a supernatural lockdown, okay?
带走科贝特的东西不想我们离开
Whatever took Corbett doesn't want us to leave.
而且那不是个死亡回声
And it's no death echo,
是个厉害的东西  它想要吓我们
this is a bad mother. It wants us scared.
或者是想要我们
Or it just wants us.
伙计们  摄影机又出故障了
Guys, the camera's fritzing again.
伙计们  电磁场开始变强了
Guys, the EMF's starting to spike.
- 这个很厉害  - 艾德
- This is a big one. - Ed.
大家靠近点  有什么要来了
Everybody stay close, there's something coming.
伙计们
Guys.
好了  我们别...
Okay, let's... Let's just stay...
伙计们  这是你们之前看到的回声吗
Guys, is this the same echo you guys saw earlier?
不  那是另一个人
No, it's a different guy.
多个回声吗  怎么回事
Multiple echoes? What the hell's going on?
我怎么知道
Beats me.
好吧  好
Okay. All right, all right, all right.
伙计
Buddy!
醒醒
Wake up.
你死了
You're dead!
- 喂  - 他干什么呢
- Hello? - What's he doing?
他干什么呢
What's he doing?
虽然不多见  但有时你能把回声吓出循环
It's rare, but sometimes you can shock an echo out of its loop...
如果你能触动鬼魂仍存留的人性
if you can talk to the part of the ghost that's still human.
但一般你得跟死者有些联系
But usually you have to have some connection to the deceased.
拜托  醒醒  死去吧
Come on, wake up! Be dead!
你们听到了吗
You guys hear that?
- 那是什么声音  - 你们听到了吗
- What's that sound? - You guys hear that?
- 那是什么  - 快醒过来
- What is that? - Snap out of it, buddy, huh?
拜托  你还等什么
Come on. What are you waiting for?
你不在了  你死了
You're gone. You're dead.
它哪去了
Where the hell did it go?
哥们  根本没有这方面的记录
Dude, there's no records of any of this.
没人在这里被枪杀
No one got shot here,
不用说  更没人在这里被火车撞死
obviously no one got run over by a frigging train.
跟紧点
Stay close.
是回声抓走了科贝特吗
Did the echoes take Corbett?
是  不  我不知道
Yes... No. I don't know.
我们不知道这怎么回事
We don't know what's doing what here...
- 我们就在查这个呢  - 跟紧了
- that's what we're trying to figure out. Okay. - Stay close.
好  听着  死亡回声是鬼
Okay, look, um, death echoes are ghosts, okay?
鬼一般停留在
Now, ghosts they usually haunt
他们生活或死去的地方
places where they lived or where they died.
- 但这些鬼既不生活在这里也没死在这里  - 嗯
- Except these mooks didn't live or die here. - Right.
那他们为什么在这里
So what are they doing here?
给这位女士根雪茄吧
Give the lady a cigar.
好了  说真的
All right. Seriously,
通过那台摄影机看这场噩梦
does looking at this nightmare through that camera
是能让你好受些吗  拜托...
make you feel better or something? I mean...
嗯  是的
Yeah. Uh, yeah, I think so.
弗里曼·戴格特  最后的屋主
Freeman Daggett, house's last owner.
正式因在甘博综合医院20年的
Officially commended for 20 years of fine service...
- 尽心服务而受此嘉奖  - 他是医生吗
- at the Gamble General Hospital. - He's a doctor?
清洁工
Janitor.
这里看来是他的窝
This looks like his den.
你说他什么时候死的  64年吗
When did you say he died? '64?
对  心脏病
Yeah. Heart attack.
这是什么  军粮吗
What are these, C rations?
军队配发  三层圆饼
Army-issued, three squares.
够吃一辈子了
Like, a lifetime supply.
天啊  他就吃这个吗
God, is that all he ate?
一站式购物
One-stop shopping.
哎呦  上锁了
Hello. Locked.
拜托  伙计们  这太荒唐了
Come on, guys, this is ridiculous.
这怎么能帮我们找到科贝特
I mean, how the hell is this supposed to find Corbett?
我们该撬开地板
We should be digging up the frigging floorboards right now.
在原子弹攻击下存活
Survival Under Atomic Attack.
真乐观
An optimist.
垃圾
Crap.
标本制作  好吧
Taxidermy. Okay.
- 你说戴格特是医院清洁工  - 嗯
- You said Daggett was a hospital janitor? - Yeah.
这里有三个身份标签
We got three toe tags here.
一人  死于枪伤
One, death by gunshots,
还有火车事故
train accident,
和自杀
and suicide.
怎么了
What?
这就能解释这里那些死亡回声了
Well, that explains why all the death echoes are here.
他们在这里是因为他们的尸体在这里
They're here because their bodies are here.
在房子里
Somewhere in the house.
什么
What?
戴格特从停尸间把尸体带了回来...
Daggett brought the remains home from the morgue
玩
to play.
真恶心  哥们
That's nasty, dude.
嗯
Right.
等等
Wait a minute.
科贝特
Corbett.
好了  玛姬
Okay, Maggie.
- 别跟大家走散  好吗  - 玛姬
- Closer to the herd, okay? - Maggie?
- 玛姬  - 她没事
- Maggie? - She's fine.
哈里  现在是8.6  还在快速飙升
Harry, Harry, I got an 8.6 and climbing fast.
有什么大东西要来了  看
Something huge is coming. Look.
有什么大东西要来了
Something big is coming.
超过11了
It's past 11, you guys.
- 怎么回事  - 谁都别动
- What is happening? - Nobody move.
别动  安静
Hold on, hold on. Stay quiet.
- 怎么回事  - 艾德
- What's going on? - Ed.
萨姆
Sam?
肯定是一股能量
Must be the surge.
萨姆
Sam?
他哪去了
Where'd he go?
不
No.
萨姆
Sam!
(抓鬼特工队)
- 萨姆  - 萨姆
- Sammy! - Sam!
- 科贝特  - 科贝特
- Corbett! - Corbett!
- 科贝特  - 说话啊
- Corbett! - Talk to us.
- 萨姆  - 萨姆
- Sammy! - Sam?
- 萨姆  - 科贝特
- Sam. - Corbett, Corbett!
科贝特
Corbett!
萨姆
Sam!
天啊  我好怕
God, I am so scared.
我好怕
I'm so scared.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
会没事的  玛姬
It's gonna be okay, Maggie.
科贝特
Corbett!
我最好的朋友
My best friend...
- 和我最好的妹妹  - 艾德
- and my best sister. - Ed.
- 哈里  - 艾德
- Harry. - Ed.
听着  艾德
Listen, Ed...
你在上我妹妹吗
Are you banging my sister?
没有
No.
- 拿着我的眼镜  - 好嘞
- Hold my glasses. - You got it.
艾德  艾德
Ed, Ed, Ed!
- 伙计们  - 艾德  放开
- Guys. - Ed, get off.
你们快停下
You guys, stop.
你们有麻烦了
You guys are in trouble.
你们干什么呢
The **** are you doing?
别闹了
Cut it out!
我们都少俩人了
We're down by two people.
萨姆
Sam!
好啊
Great.
萨姆
Sammy!
抱歉
Sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我眼镜在你手里
You got my glasses.
- 他打到我的牙了吗  - 没有
- He got my tooth there? - Uh, no.
- 我赢了吧  - 是的  你很棒
- I won that, right? - Yup, you're good.
- 谢了  斯布鲁斯  - 嗯  都怪我
- Thanks, Spruce. - Yeah, it's my fault.
好啊  真好  谢谢了
Great. That's nice. Thanks.
科贝特
Corbett.
醒醒  伙计
Wake up, man.
科贝特
Corbett.
- 科贝特  - 萨姆
- Corbett, hey. - Sam?
听好我的声音  好吗
You gotta keep listening to my voice, okay?
我在这里呢
I'm right here.
保持清醒
Stay awake.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
疼痛会停止  所以别担心
It stops hurting, so don't worry.
科贝特  保持清醒
Corbett, stay with me.
- 保持清醒  好吗  我在这里  - 萨姆
- Stay with me, you got it? I'm right here. - Sam.
保持清醒  别
Stay with me. Don't.
别  不
Don't. No!
科贝特
Corbett!
不
No.
科贝特
Corbett!
- 科贝特  - 你们去哪了
- Corbett! - Where'd you guys go?
你们在哪
Where are you guys?
迪恩  你在干什么
Dean, what are you doing?
好吧  戴格特是个冷战疯子  是吧
Okay. So Daggett was a Cold-War nut. Okay?
还是业余标本师
He was an amateur taxidermist.
他喜欢跟尸体慢舞
He liked to slow dance with cadavers
只吃军粮
and all he ate was C rations.
所以我们究竟要找什么
So what the hell are we looking for?
- 好悲惨的生活  - 孤独的生活
- A horrible little life. - A lonely life.
冷战生活
A Cold-War life.
他很怕
He was scared.
- 他很怕  - 怕什么
- He was scared. He was scared. - Scared of what?
- 怎么了  - 迪恩  你去哪
- What? What? - Dean, where are you going?
- 等等  别丢下我  - 等等
- Wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't leave me in here. - Wait.
- 迪恩  - 伙计们
- Dean! - Guys.
离我远点
Get away from me.
不会疼的
This won't hurt.
没事的
It's okay.
放松
Relax.
你去哪
Where are you going?
在当时  戴格特这样的人
Guys like Daggett back then,
特别害怕苏联人的人
the ones who are really scared of the Russkies...
他们会建防空洞
they built bomb shelters.
我猜他就建了一个
I'm guessing he's got one.
我敢说是在地下室
I'll bet you it's in the basement.
这不好笑  多少次...
That is not funny. How many times...?
- 是谁关了门  - 是它
- Who closed the door? - It did.
它想把我们分开
It wants to separate us.
- 艾德  听好了  - 什么
- Ed, listen to me. - What?
我的行李袋里有盐
There's some salt in my duffle.
画个圈  然后站进去
Make a circle and get inside.
- 进他的...  - 什么啊
- Inside his...? - That's stupid.
站进你的行李袋里吗
Inside your duffle bag?
盐圈  你个蠢蛋
In the salt, you idiot!
- 好  - 好好
- Okay. - Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
快  进盐圈
Hurry up. Get in the circle, get in the circle.
来  快
Come on, come on. Quick, quick.
伙计们  我不想死  好吗
Guys, guys, I don't wanna die, okay?
我也不想你...
And I don't want you...
听我说
Listen to me, okay?
听好  如果我们不死...
Listen, if we don't die...
那我完全不介意你上我妹妹
it's totally okay if you, uh, do my sister.
好啊
Nice.
伙计们
Guys. Hey, guys.
它又来了
It's coming again.
好  靠紧
Okay. Oh, God. Get in close.
- 靠紧  - 怎么总发生这事
- Get in close. - Why does this keep happening?
怎么总发生这事
Why does this keep happening?
天啊
My God.
God.
天啊
科贝特
Corbett.
可以问你件事吗
Can I ask you something?
什么事
What?
之前  你和萨姆
Earlier, you and Sam.
他说你还剩两个月了
He said you had two months left?
嗯  说来话长
Yeah. It's complicated.
之前  萨姆
A while ago, Sam...
不不  我才不要...
No, no, no. I'm not gonna...
向个破真人秀
whine about my ******** problems...
抱怨我的麻烦
to some ******** reality show.
我要好好工作
I'm gonna do my ******* job.
- 是癌症吗  - 闭嘴
- Is it cancer? - Shut up.
你听到了吗
You hear that?
我一直在等有更多朋友来
I've been waiting for some more friends.
我好孤单
I get lonely.
但你会来参加我的派对吧
But you're coming to my party, aren't you?
那是音乐吗
Is that music?
对  是墙后传来的
Yeah. It's coming from behind this wall.
你好强壮
You're strong.
你会在这里待很久
You'll stay a good, long time.
萨姆
Sam!
迪恩
Dean.
天啊
My God.
不  科贝特
No. Corbett.
(抓鬼特工队)
天啊  我们做了什么啊
God, what have we done?
- 科贝特  - 艾德
- Corbett. - Ed. Ed.
- 嗯  - 科贝特是死亡回声了
- Yeah? - Corbett's... He's a death echo.
他在重现自己的被杀
He's, uh, reliving his own murder.
一遍又一遍直到永远
Over and over forever.
这个戴格特有什么毛病啊
What's this Daggett guy's problem anyway?
孤独
Loneliness.
- 他没听说过充气娃娃吗  - 不
- Has he never heard of a RealDoll? - No, no, no.
戴格特是《惊魂记》把老妈做成标本那么孤独
Daggett was the Norman Bates, stuff-your-mother kind of lonely.
所以他才从停尸房偷走了尸体
I mean, that's why he lifted these bodies from the morgue.
给自己办生日派对
He threw himself a birthday party,
但只有他们肯来
except they were the only ones who would come.
反正  午夜时
Anyway, so at midnight,
他把他们封在了防空洞里  然后上了楼
he sealed them in the bomb shelter and went upstairs,
服了过多马镇静剂而死
and OD'd on horse tranqs.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
他告诉我的
Because he told me.
嗯
Yeah.
好吧  他死了之后  怎么
Okay, so now that he's dead, what?
换汤不换药
Same song, different verse,
还想继续拉人来他的派对吗
trying to get people to come to his party?
差不多吧  永远留下
Pretty much, yeah. Stay forever.
那是真子弹吗
Those real bullets?
是岩盐
It's rock salt.
抓鬼特工队
Ghostfacers
我们去其他人不肯去的地方
We go to places where others will not
抓鬼特工队
Ghostfacers
冲入险境  不顾危险
Stay in the kitchen When the kitchen gets hot
伙计们
Guys.
不
No.
科贝特
Corbett.
等等  伙计们
Wait, guys.
伙计们  那是科贝特
Guys, it's... It's Corbett.
他困住了
He's... He's trapped.
他很痛苦  我们得...想办法...
He's in a lot of pain, you know? We gotta... We gotta try and...
想办法帮他脱离循环
We got to try and pull him out of his loop.
我们必须那么做
We have to.
艾德
Ed.
科贝特
Corbett?
Corbett, it's...
- 天啊  - 别出盐圈
- God. - Don't cross the line of salt.
我必须去  哈里
I gotta do it, Harry.
科贝特  听我说
Corbett, listen to me.
我不会伤害你的
Okay, I'm not gonna hurt you.
听我说
Listen.
听我说  天啊
Listen. Oh, God.
科贝特
Corbett.
- 天啊  - 退回来
- My God. - Get back. Get back. Get back. Get back.
我做不到
I can't, okay?
他听不到  他总在不断死去
He's not hearing me, okay? He won't stop dying.
不是吧
Seriously?
你还在拍
You're still shooting?
这让他好受点  别问了
It makes him feel better. Don't ask.
天啊
God.
伙计们  进入捉鬼状态
Hell, guys. Get in your ghost role thing.
有什么要来了
Something's coming.
天啊
My God.
我知道我们要怎么触动他了
I... I know how we can get through to him.
怎么做
How?
艾德
Ed.
他对你有感情
He had feelings for you.
他想要你
He wanted you.
什么...
Wha...?
- 要我做什么  - 你知道的
- Wanted me to what? - You know.
不知道
No.
你知道你得怎么做
And you know what you've gotta do.
你可以的  艾德
You can do it, Ed.
你一直是勇敢的那个
You've always been the brave one.
你可以的  你激励了我们也勇敢起来
Yes, you can. You make us brave.
- 玛姬  是吧  - 是的
- Maggie, right? - Yeah.
- 嗯  - 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah, you do.
绝对是的
You totally do.
艾德
Ed...
你得为那个可怜的死掉的实习生基一把
You gotta go be gay for that poor, dead intern.
你得让他走入光明
You gotta send him into the light.
科贝特
Corbett.
玛姬  不
Maggie. No, no, Maggie.
不  没事的  别担心
No, it's okay. Don't worry.
科贝特  听着
Corbett, look.
是艾德  伙计
Okay, it's just Ed, buddy.
是我
It's just me.
科贝特  听我说
Corbett, listen to me.
听我说  我...我们...
Listen to me. I'm... We...
好
Okay.
你对...
You meant...
科贝特  你对团队很重要
Corbett, you meant a lot to the team.
你对...
You meant...
你对我很重要
You meant a lot to me.
你从不退缩
You know, never ever back down...
你从不发火  好吗  这我都记得  科贝特
never say a bad word, okay? I remember that, Corbett. I...
我都记得  我记得因为我爱你  科贝特
I remember that. I remember because I love you, Corbett.
我真心地爱你
I really, truly love you.
你记得吗
Do you remember that?
Do you?
- 艾德  - 嗯
- Ed? - Yeah.
嗯  科贝特
Yeah, Corbett, it's...
科贝特  是我
Corbett, yeah, it's me.
是我  看着我
It's me. Look at me.
你得帮帮我们
You gotta help us, man.
你得帮帮我们  科贝特  求你
You have to help us, Corbett. Please. Please.
求你帮帮我们吧
Please help us right now.
别紧张  没事吧
Take it easy. You all right?
伙计们
Guys.
过来
Come here!
这可不妙  很不妙
This is bad. Very bad.
科贝特
Corbett?
你没事吧  哥们
You all right, dude?
你没事吧
You all right?
天啊
My God.
(抓鬼特工队)
闰年  2月29日  默顿大宅
Leap year, February 29th, the Morton House.
悲惨的一天
A tragic day.
鬼魂们在这天饱受折磨
A day of souls bound in torment...
生命在这天面临威胁
of lives held in cruel balance.
但抓鬼特工队  他们尽了全力
But the Ghostfacers, they did the best that they could.
我们失去了一位好朋友
We lost a beloved friend...
但我们得到了新盟友
but we gained new allies.
我们知道
We know this much:
每天  包括今天  都是新的开始
That every day, including today, is a new beginning.
我们在默顿大宅的
We learned more than we can
惨痛教训中所学到的是难以言说的
say in the brutal feat of the Morton House.
抓鬼特工队
The Ghostfacers
被迫面对了比鬼更可怕的东西
were forced to face something far more scary than ghosts.
他们被迫面对了自己
They were forced to face themselves.
战争会改变男人
War changes man.
还有玛姬
And Maggie.
战争会改变男人
War changes man...
还有一个女人
and one woman.
科贝特  我们...
You know, Corbett, we just...
天啊  我们想认为
gosh, we just like to think
你在守护着我们
that you're out there watching over us.
在我们看来  你不是实习生了
As far as we're concerned, you're not an intern anymore.
你绝对赢得了做一名抓鬼特工队正式成员的权利
You have more than earned full Ghostfacer status.
- 而且队里有个鬼也挺酷的  - 是啊
- Plus it'd cool to have a ghost on the team. - Yeah.
我们还以为
And here we were thinking that, you know,
是我们在教你
we were teaching you and...
但其实一直以来  是你在教我们
all this time, you were teaching us...
教我们爱
about heart...
教我们奉献
about dedication.
还有
About...
同性之爱能穿透阴阳之隔
how gay love can pierce through the veil of death and
拯救大家
save the day.
谢谢  阿伦·J·科贝特
Thank you, Alan J. Corbett.
好好走入满天星斗的夜空吧  小伙子
Go well into that starry night, young Turk.
好好去吧
Go well.
(月度最佳员工)
行了  斯布鲁斯  我还得收拾东西呢
Come on, Spruce, I gotta get all this stuff packed up.
怎么了  边收拾边说吧
So? Pack and talk.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
想到什么说什么
Say what comes to mind.
这是我们的心声时刻  科贝特  吐露心声吧
This is one of our confessional moments, Corbett, so confess.
你觉得今晚会发生什么
What'd you think was gonna happen tonight?
你觉得今晚之行会发生什么
What do you think's gonna happen tonight on this trip?
我觉得今晚
I think tonight...
真的
I really do.
我觉得我们的梦想都将成真
I think all our dreams are gonna come true.
那听上去很傻吗
Does that sound stupid?
是有点
Kind of does, yeah.
(缅怀阿伦·J·科贝特  1985年到2008年  不可能之王)
你们觉得怎么样
So guys, what do you think?
你还好吗
You all right?
我觉得还算不错呢
You know, I kind of think it was half awesome.
还算不错  那就是好了吧
Half awesome. That's full-on good, right?
嗯  简直不可思议  你们能...
Yeah. I mean, it's bizarre how y'all are able to, uh...
致敬科贝特的回忆
to honor Corbett's memory
同时狠狠地利用了他的死亡  好样的
while grossly exploiting the manner of his death. Well done.
是啊  你的平衡保持得真好
Yeah. No, it's a real tight rope you guys are walking.
嗯  好了  各位
Yeah. All right, guys.
不  那是现实
No, that's reality, man.
嗯  科贝特为寻求真相献出生命
Yeah. Corbett gave his life searching for the truth...
我们的工作就是把它展示给世界
and it is our job over here to share it with the world.
嗯  根据我们的经验
Right. Well, um, our experience,
知道你向世界展示真相时会得到什么吗
you know what you get when you show the world the truth?
束身衣  或面门一拳
A straitjacket or a punch in the face.
- 有时两个都有  - 对
- Sometimes both. - Right.
得了  两位  别做特工队黑
Come on, guys, don't be Facer haters
就因为我们刚好拍到了世纪最劲爆影像
because we happened to have gotten the footage of the century.
是啊
Yeah.
- 这我们无话可说了  - 是啊
- You got us there. - Yeah.
嗯  那回头见了
Yeah. Well, we'll see you guys around.
嗯
Yeah.
回见
Peace out.
混蛋
Dicks.
是啊
Yeah.
- 绝对是  - 嗯
- Totally. - Yep.
我们开始拷贝吧
Let's start laying off some DVDs.
听上去是个好主意  斯布鲁斯
That sounds like a good idea, Spruce.
伙计们  我觉得我们会需要更大的办公室
You know, guys, I think we're gonna need a bigger office here.
因为我们要走向全国
You know, because we're gonna go national,
然后再走向全世界
and then it's gonna go international, and...
那俩家伙落了舞蹈包
Menudo left their dance bag behind.
里面有什么
What's inside?
这是什么玩意
What the hell is this?
我这里似乎出了技术故障
Seem to be having some technical difficulty over here.
- 等等  - 不不不
- Wait, wait, wait. - No, no, no.
- 等等  - 不
- Wait! Wait! Wait! - No.
"没有操作系统"  等等
"No operating system found"? Wait a minute.
- 没问题了吧  - 不
- We clean? - No!
- 开玩笑吗  - 不
- Are you kidding me? - No.
这不可能
This can't be happening.
- 哈里  - 不
- Harry. Harry. - No!
电磁铁  抹掉他们所有的录像带和硬盘
Electromagnet. Wiped out every tape and hard drive they have.
世界还没准备好迎来抓鬼特工队
World just isn't ready for the Ghostfacers.
真可惜  我还挺喜欢这节目的
That's too bad, I kind of liked the show.
也有高光时刻
Had its moments.
稳赚了
That is money in the bank.